# Sanjeev Kumar

# **ADDRESS**

A-17, Jay Ambey Nagar, Thaltej, Gujarat, Pin-380054

# **EDUCATION**

# IIMT UNIVERSITY, MEERUT

B.Tech IN COMPUTER SCIENCE July 2017- July 2021 | Meerut Marks: 76.75%

#### A N S S SMARAK S S SCHOOL

SSC IN SCIENCE

July 2014- July 2016 | Saharsa Marks : 60.2%

#### **ZILA SCHOOL SAHARSA**

HSC IN ALL SUBJECT July 2011- July 2012 | Saharsa Marks: 67.8%

## LINKS

LinkedIn://sanjeevkumar12 Github://sanjeevkumar70 Twitter://sanju52632868 Instagram://sk\_arya70

# **COURSEWORK**

#### **GRADUATE**

Created AutoInsurance website Using java technology , user could Book insurance policy according to Own choice.

# **SKILLS**

- React is
- Javascript
- Html
- Css
- Bootstrap
- Sass
- Json
- Git
- Restful Api
- GraphQL

#### **SUMMARY**

I am an enthusiastic and passionate web developer. I pursued my B.tech degree in Computer Science.my main specialization is doing Web Development.I put dedication in every project that I do. And I hope my dedication will help me to explore my expertise, and to boost up my career plan

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### **TECHERUDITE** | REACT JS DEVELOPER

Dec 2022 - Present | Ahmedabad, Gujarat

In-depth knowledge of Javascript, React js, & web technologies such as HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Restful Api, Graphql and others

#### **DENTSU WORLD SERVICES** | REACT JS DEVELOPER

May 2022 - Oct 2022 | Pune, MH

#### Ui components designing

Identified Web-based user interactions and developed responsive user interface components via React Concepts.

#### **UGAM SOLUTION PVT. LTD** | FRONT END or REACT JS DEVELOPER

July 2021 - May 2022 | Mumbai, MH

Designed multiple dynamic and browser compatible pages using Html, Css, Javascript, React js. I have Worked on the Nestle water project, In Html, Css, Javascript, Bootstrap to plan, to design and develop the user interface.

### **PROJECT**

#### **FACES PROJECTS**

Dec 2022 - Present

The project included complete redesign of their website, and adopting the standard styling according to client requirement.

#### **NESTLE PURELIFE PROJECTS**

Order you water Online! Explore & shop from a wide variety of water products, coolers, accessories and services from Nestle Waters. Technology Used: Html, Css, Javascript.

#### **NESTLE WATER PROJECTS**

The project included complete redesign of their website, and adopting the standard styling according to client requirement.

#### CERTIFICATION

#### Certificate of Completion in Web Development by INCAPP

This certificate was issued by INCAPP after completing 3 months training in Web Design Technology successfully.

# **LANGUAGE**

- English
- Hindi